const questions = [{
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '見る',
        choiceA: 'だします',
        choiceB: 'だします',
        choiceC: 'へいじつ',
        choiceD: 'みます',
        correctAnswer: 'みます',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '診る',
        choiceA: 'こっかいぎじどう',
        choiceB: 'うちゅうひこうし',
        choiceC: 'うちゅうひこうし',
        choiceD: 'みます',
        correctAnswer: 'みます',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '捜す',
        choiceA: 'べん　（ほうげん）',
        choiceB: 'みます',
        choiceC: 'ガス',
        choiceD: 'さがします',
        correctAnswer: 'さがします',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '探す',
        choiceA: 'ごみ',
        choiceB: 'へいじつ',
        choiceC: 'ばしょ',
        choiceD: 'さがします',
        correctAnswer: 'さがします',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '時間に遅れる',
        choiceA: 'フリーマーケット',
        choiceB: 'ちょくせつ',
        choiceC: 'なんでも',
        choiceD: 'おくれます',
        correctAnswer: 'おくれます',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '会議に間に合う',
        choiceA: 'なんでも',
        choiceB: 'こわい',
        choiceC: 'かたづきます',
        choiceD: 'まにあいます',
        correctAnswer: 'まにあいます',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '宿題をやる',
        choiceA: 'ひろいます',
        choiceB: 'ちがいます',
        choiceC: 'がいしゃ',
        choiceD: 'やります',
        correctAnswer: 'やります',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: 'ごみを拾う',
        choiceA: 'かん',
        choiceB: 'うちゅう',
        choiceC: 'ぼんおどり',
        choiceD: 'ひろいます',
        correctAnswer: 'ひろいます',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '学校に連絡する',
        choiceA: 'よこ',
        choiceB: 'さいふ',
        choiceC: 'なんでも',
        choiceD: 'れんらくします',
        correctAnswer: 'れんらくします',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '気分がいい',
        choiceA: 'へいじつ',
        choiceB: 'かたづきます',
        choiceC: 'うちゅう',
        choiceD: 'きぶんがいい',
        correctAnswer: 'きぶんがいい',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '気分が悪い',
        choiceA: 'おきば',
        choiceB: 'ずいぶん',
        choiceC: 'こんど',
        choiceD: 'きぶんがわるい',
        correctAnswer: 'きぶんがわるい',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '運動会',
        choiceA: 'ガス',
        choiceB: 'へいじつ',
        choiceC: 'ぼんおどり',
        choiceD: 'うんどうかい',
        correctAnswer: 'うんどうかい',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '盆踊り',
        choiceA: 'ガス',
        choiceB: 'さがします',
        choiceC: 'まにあいます',
        choiceD: 'ぼんおどり',
        correctAnswer: 'ぼんおどり',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'よこ',
        choiceB: 'ぼんおどり',
        choiceC: 'なんでも',
        choiceD: 'フリーマーケット',
        correctAnswer: 'フリーマーケット',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '場所',
        choiceA: 'フリーマーケット',
        choiceB: 'かん',
        choiceC: 'よこ',
        choiceD: 'ばしょ',
        correctAnswer: 'ばしょ',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'みます',
        choiceB: 'うんどうかい',
        choiceC: 'あんな…',
        choiceD: 'ボランティア',
        correctAnswer: 'ボランティア',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '財布',
        choiceA: 'へいじつ',
        choiceB: 'ボランティア',
        choiceC: 'うちゅうせん',
        choiceD: 'さいふ',
        correctAnswer: 'さいふ',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'ずいぶん',
        choiceB: 'さがします',
        choiceC: 'かん',
        choiceD: 'ごみ',
        correctAnswer: 'ごみ',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '国会議事堂',
        choiceA: 'がいしゃ',
        choiceB: 'こんな…',
        choiceC: 'きぶんがわるい',
        choiceD: 'こっかいぎじどう',
        correctAnswer: 'こっかいぎじどう',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '平日/週末',
        choiceA: 'がいしゃ',
        choiceB: 'こんど',
        choiceC: 'やります',
        choiceD: 'へいじつ',
        correctAnswer: 'へいじつ',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '大阪弁(方言）',
        choiceA: 'まにあいます',
        choiceB: 'へいじつ',
        choiceC: 'まにあいます',
        choiceD: 'べん　（ほうげん）',
        correctAnswer: 'べん　（ほうげん）',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '今度',
        choiceA: 'なんでも',
        choiceB: 'ぼんおどり',
        choiceC: 'みます',
        choiceD: 'こんど',
        correctAnswer: 'こんど',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'びん',
        choiceB: 'へいじつ',
        choiceC: 'こんな…',
        choiceD: 'ずいぶん',
        correctAnswer: 'ずいぶん',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '直接',
        choiceA: 'さま',
        choiceB: 'ごみ',
        choiceC: 'こんな…',
        choiceD: 'ちょくせつ',
        correctAnswer: 'ちょくせつ',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'みます',
        choiceB: 'こんな…',
        choiceC: 'へいじつ',
        choiceD: 'いつでも',
        correctAnswer: 'いつでも',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'どこでも',
        choiceB: 'ガス',
        choiceC: 'ばしょ',
        choiceD: 'どこでも',
        correctAnswer: 'どこでも',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'さいふ',
        choiceB: 'みます',
        choiceC: 'びん',
        choiceD: 'だれでも',
        correctAnswer: 'だれでも',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'こっかいぎじどう',
        choiceB: 'やります',
        choiceC: 'べん　（ほうげん）',
        choiceD: 'なんでも',
        correctAnswer: 'なんでも',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'よこ',
        choiceB: 'かん',
        choiceC: 'うちゅう',
        choiceD: 'こんな…',
        correctAnswer: 'こんな…',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'ちがいます',
        choiceB: 'ガス',
        choiceC: 'ちがいます',
        choiceD: 'そんな…',
        correctAnswer: 'そんな…',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'どこでも',
        choiceB: 'へいじつ',
        choiceC: 'おくれます',
        choiceD: 'あんな…',
        correctAnswer: 'あんな…',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '片付く',
        choiceA: 'さいふ',
        choiceB: 'ひろいます',
        choiceC: 'いつでも',
        choiceD: 'かたづきます',
        correctAnswer: 'かたづきます',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '出す',
        choiceA: 'どこでも',
        choiceB: 'こわい',
        choiceC: 'なんでも',
        choiceD: 'だします',
        correctAnswer: 'だします',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '燃えるごみ',
        choiceA: 'やります',
        choiceB: 'ひろいます',
        choiceC: 'だします',
        choiceD: 'もえるごみ',
        correctAnswer: 'もえるごみ',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '置き場',
        choiceA: 'ちょくせつ',
        choiceB: 'だれでも',
        choiceC: 'かん',
        choiceD: 'おきば',
        correctAnswer: 'おきば',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '横',
        choiceA: 'こんな…',
        choiceB: 'さがします',
        choiceC: 'うちゅう',
        choiceD: 'よこ',
        correctAnswer: 'よこ',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '瓶',
        choiceA: 'さいふ',
        choiceB: 'さがします',
        choiceC: 'うちゅうせん',
        choiceD: 'びん',
        correctAnswer: 'びん',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '缶',
        choiceA: 'だします',
        choiceB: 'こっかいぎじどう',
        choiceC: 'まにあいます',
        choiceD: 'かん',
        correctAnswer: 'かん',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '',
        choiceA: 'なんでも',
        choiceB: 'うちゅうせん',
        choiceC: 'さいふ',
        choiceD: 'ガス',
        correctAnswer: 'ガス',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: 'ガス会社',
        choiceA: 'へいじつ',
        choiceB: 'なんでも',
        choiceC: 'きぶんがいい',
        choiceD: 'がいしゃ',
        correctAnswer: 'がいしゃ',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '宇宙',
        choiceA: 'ごみ',
        choiceB: 'もえるごみ',
        choiceC: 'きぶんがいい',
        choiceD: 'うちゅう',
        correctAnswer: 'うちゅう',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '田中様、お客様',
        choiceA: 'うちゅうせん',
        choiceB: 'ちょくせつ',
        choiceC: 'もえるごみ',
        choiceD: 'さま',
        correctAnswer: 'さま',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '宇宙船',
        choiceA: 'うちゅうせん',
        choiceB: 'ずいぶん',
        choiceC: 'れんらくします',
        choiceD: 'うちゅうせん',
        correctAnswer: 'うちゅうせん',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '怖い',
        choiceA: 'いつでも',
        choiceB: 'フリーマーケット',
        choiceC: 'ちょくせつ',
        choiceD: 'こわい',
        correctAnswer: 'こわい',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '違う',
        choiceA: 'ぼんおどり',
        choiceB: 'うんどうかい',
        choiceC: 'ガス',
        choiceD: 'ちがいます',
        correctAnswer: 'ちがいます',
    },
    {
        question: 'What mean?',
        imgSrc: '宇宙飛行士',
        choiceA: 'だします',
        choiceB: 'ばしょ',
        choiceC: 'ぼんおどり',
        choiceD: 'うちゅうひこうし',
        correctAnswer: 'うちゅうひこうし',
    },
]